<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="protocol_title0">Important：</string>
    <string name="protocol_title1">1.Important tips</string>
    <string name="protocol_title2">2.Use restrictions</string>
    <string name="protocol_title3">3.Reservation of rights</string>
    <string name="protocol_title4">4.Limitation of Liability</string>
    <string name="protocol_title5">5.Dispute Resolution and the legal basis</string>

    <string name="protocol_detail0">
        &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Important: This agreement is for you (individual, company or any other entity) and Shenzhen Bankledger Technology Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “SafeGem”) on signing an end user license agreement for the use of SafeGem Wallet (hereinafter referred to as “the Agreement”). Please read this agreement carefully before using your SafeGem wallet. Your use of SafeGem Wallet will be deemed to have been agreed to be bound by the terms described in this Agreement. If you do not agree to this agreement, please do not use SafeGem wallet. Subject to the SafeGem return policy, you can request a return. Return Policy must be in accordance with relevant laws and regulations of the purchasing country / region.
    </string>

    <string name="protocol_detail1">
        &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Before you use your SafeGem wallet, please read the instructions carefully and back up your seed password and payment password yourself after creating the wallet. Keep your password and wallet in a safe place. In order to ensure that SafeGem wallet is absolutely safe, SafeGem cannot obtain your password and payment password. It is because of this security mechanism that SafeGem can\'t provide you with password recovery function. If you personally directly or indirectly cause the seed password, payment password, SafeGem wallet to be lost, forgotten or stolen, all risks, liabilities, losses, expenses, etc. caused by this shall be borne by you.
    </string>

    <string name="protocol_detail2">
        &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;2.1 You may not use SafeGem\'s technology or intellectual property to design, develop, manufacture, or sell third party equipment / accessories or licenses associated with SafeGem Wallet without prior permission from SafeGem.\n&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;2.2 Unless expressly permitted otherwise, you may not and agree that no other person may copy, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble or create derivative works of SafeGem Wallet.\n &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;2.3 You agree to abide by all applicable laws and regulations of the country in which the wallet resides or is used when using SafeGem Wallet.
    </string>

    <string name="protocol_detail3">
        &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;SafeGem and its licensor enjoy and retain all rights and eligibility to SafeGem Wallet and retain any other rights not expressly granted to you by this Agreement.\n&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;You acknowledge that the wallet is provided "as is", there is no express or implied warranty of any kind, and to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, SafeGem, its licensor / copyright holder or its subsidiaries does not provide any express or implied representations or warranties, including but not limited to warranties of merchantability, satisfactory quality, fitness for a particular purpose, accuracy, confidentiality and non-infringement of third party rights. SafeGem or any other party does not guarantee that the features contained in the wallet will meet your requirements or that the operation of the wallet will not be interrupted or error. It is your responsibility to choose this wallet to achieve the desired results and all the responsibilities and risks associated with using this wallet and obtaining results.
    </string>

    <string name="protocol_detail4">
        &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;4.1 For problems in use of SafeGem wallet caused by abuse, misuse or unauthorized modifications, SafeGem does not assume any responsibility.\n&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;4.2 Under the circumstances of any profit, income, loss of sales, loss of data or cost, property damage, personal injury, business interruption, loss of business information of purchase on substitute goods or services caused by the use or inability to use the wallet, or any special, direct, indirect, incidental, economic, cover-up, punitive, special or subordinate damage, regardless of the theory of responsibility (contract, infringement, negligence or otherwise) to the extent that it is not expressly prohibited by applicable law, SafeGem and its employees, licensors or affiliates are not liable, even if they have been advised of the possibility of such damage. Some jurisdictions do not allow limited liability for personal injury, incidental or consequential damages, and this limitation may not apply to you.\n&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;4.3 SafeGem\'s total liability limit for all damages (except for personal injury or death caused by SafeGem\'s negligence, subject to applicable law) does not exceed the price paid by you for the purchase of SafeGem equipment.
    </string>

    <string name="protocol_detail5">
         &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;5.1 The Agreement is governed by the relevant laws of the People\'s Republic of China, and construed in accordance with these laws.\n &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;5.2 Result of this agreement all disputes arising out of or related thereto shall first be resolved through friendly consultation agreement between the two sides. If the negotiation fails, you should submit a dispute or controversy to people\'s court within the jurisdiction of SafeGem (Shenzhen Nanshan District) to resolve.
    </string>
</resources>